Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4212
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America AFL-CIO, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  April 13 1962 - October 29 1968
- National Society of Professional Engineers, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  May 30 1978
- International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  September 21 1977
- Public Services International, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  October 21 1963 - January 25 1967
- Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  March 25 1963 - January 22 1969
- Quebec Federation of Labour (Box 4, Folder 103)
  English and French.
- American Radio Association, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  June 26 1968 - January 11 1972
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1964-1971 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  September 8 1964 - December 7 1971
- Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  January 23 and June 22 1965
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  October 10 1967
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1963-1973 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  December 3 1963 - June 19 1973
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  April 6 1962 - June 2 1964
- Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1957-1966 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  November 13 1957 - March 11 1966
- Railway Patrolmen's International Union, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Philip A. Randolph, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  May 7 1969 - June 2 1969
- Retail Clerks International Association, 1963-1978 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  September 6 1963 - June 29 1978
- Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees Union, 1963-1977 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  October 10 1963 - June 10 1977
- Rochester, NY and Vicinity Labor Council, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  November 8 1964
- United Slate, Tile and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers' Association, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 116)
- United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1962-1969 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  November 2 1962 - June 2 1969
- Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 118)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America AFL-CIO, 1963-1978 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  January 7 1963 - January 4 1978
- International Union of Seafarers Petroleum Workers, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  August 24 1959 - March 1 1965
- Service Employees' International Union, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  April 1 1969 - January 20 1972
- Service Employees International Union National Union of Police Officers, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  March 20 1972
- Sheet Metal Workers' International Association AFL-CIO, 1962-1972 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  February 12 1962 - January 4 1972
- Shingle weaver, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  September 28 1966
- United Shoe Workers of America, 1961-1976 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  January 3 1961 - May 6 1976
- United Shoe and Boot Workers Union, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  July 10 1969 - January 18 1972
- South Dakota Federation of Labor, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 127)
- International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the US and Canada, 1963-1972 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  March 27 1963 - January 12 1972
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1962-1978 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  September 17 1962 - May 5 1978
- United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  November 28 1962 - June 23 1976
- International Stereotypers and Electrotypers, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  May 18 1962 - October 26 1965
- United Stone and Allied Product Workers, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  November 18 1964 - November 17 1967
- American Federation of Teachers, 1961-1973 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  July 20 1961 - June 22 1973
- Ithaca Teachers Association, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  October 16 1972
- New York State United Teachers, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  February 9 1976 - April 21 1976
- United Federation of Teachers, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  May 8 1962 - February 23 1968
- Chicago Local 1 Teacher Union, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  September 6 1963 - February 10 1966
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1950-1976 (Box 4, Folder 138)
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  January 19 1978 - February 20 1981
- Telecommunications International Union, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  December 1 1975
- United Telegraph Workers, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  January 11 1972
- Alliance of Independent Telephone Unions, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  June 6 1960 - August 4 1965
- Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 143)
- Tennessee State Labor Council, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  March 3 1969
- Texas State AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  February and October 1967
- United textile Workers of America AFL-CIO (Box 4, Folder 146)
- Union of American Textile Workers AFL-CIO, 1959-1968 (Box 4, Folder 147)
- Tile, Marble Terrazzo Shipmen and Finishers International Union, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 148)
- International Association of Tool Craftsmen, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  March 1 1969
- Trades Union Congress, 1961-1966 (Box 4, Folder 150)
- Trades Union Congress, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  April June and October 1967
- Trade Union Congress of the Philippines, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  February 10 1978
- American Train Dispatchers Association, 1955-1968 (Box 4, Folder 153)
- Transit Supervisors Organization, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  September 8 and 12 1969
- Transport Workers Union of America AFL-CIO, 1962-1972 (Box 4, Folder 155)
- Transportation Communication Employees Union, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 156)
- United Transportation Union, 1969-1977 (Box 4, Folder 157)
- National Treasury Employees Union, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  June 14 1976
- Truck Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Union of Chicago and Vicinity, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 159)
- International Typographical Union, 1963-1977 (Box 4, Folder 160)
- Typographical Union, Ithaca Local No. 379, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  April 8 and 11 1963
- Typographical Union, New York No. 6, 1963-1977 (Box 4, Folder 162)
- Union Democracy in Action, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  January February and March 1964
- Union Labor Life Insurance Co., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  July 19 and August 29 1963
- United Community Funds and Councils of America, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 165)
- Universal Alliance of Diamond Workers (Box 4, Folder 166)
- Upholsters' International Union, 1960-1977 (Box 4, Folder 167)
- Utility Workers Union of America, 1962-1972 (Box 4, Folder 168)
- Virginia State AFL-CIO, 1962-1973 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  October 30 1962 - October 1 1973
- Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  December 20 1967
- Welders Union, International United, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  June 13 1962 - May 11 1967
- Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  June 9 and 15 1972
- William Green Human Relations Library, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  March 23 1960
- Wisconsin State AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  January 26 1968
- International Woodworkers of America, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  December 18 1963 - October 10 1967
- Workers Defense League, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  November 1964 - August 4 1965
- World Federation of Trade Unions, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  July 1 1968
- Writers Guild of America, 1964-1976 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  September 28 1964 - November 5 1976
- Wyoming State AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 179)
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Agricultural Workers Union, 1953-1956 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  April 7 1953 - June 26 1956
- Union Correspondence. Air Carrier Communications Operators Association, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  January 11 1952
- Union Correspondence. Aircraft Workers' Alliance, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 182)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Air Line Agents Association, International, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  January 31 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Air Line Dispatchers Association, 1949-1959 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  November 30 1949 - July 29 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Air Line Employees Association, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 185)
  May 25 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  May 5 1955
- Union Correspondence. Airline Communication Employees Association, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  December 13 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Air Line Pilots Association, International, 1945-1961 (Box 4, Folder 188)
  November 10 1945 - May 4 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Alabama Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  November 11 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Aluminum Workers International Union, 1953-1962 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  May 8 1953 - January 3 1962
- Union Correspondence. Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  April 1 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Labor World, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  February 22 1951 - September 25 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Federation of Technical Engineers Architects and Draftsmen Union, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  September and November 1949
- Union Correspondence. Arizona State AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  February 7 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Arkansas State Federation Labor Council, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  August 22 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Asbestos Workers International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators AFL, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 196)
  January 26 and March 16 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Associated Unions of America, 1951-1958 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  July 2 1951 - March 20 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Association of Labor Health Administrators, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 198)
  March 7 1956 - March 21 1956
- Union Correspondence. Authors League of America, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 199)
  December 14 1953 - January 13 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Baker Workers, 1958-1961 (Box 4, Folder 200)
  September 29 1958 - August 4 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Barbers and Beauty Culturists Union of America CIO, 1947-1960 (Box 4, Folder 201)
  December 30 1947 - November 10 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. The Journeymen, Barbers, Hairdressers and Cosmetologists International Union of America, 1947-1958 (Box 4, Folder 202)
  December 30 1947 - July 3 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Alliance of Bill Posters, Billers and Distributors, 1947-1952 (Box 4, Folder 203)
  December 31 1947 - October 20 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers and Helpers AFL, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 204)
  December 30 1947 - November 21 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, iron Ship Builders and Helpers of America, 1948-1961 (Box 4, Folder 205)
  February 9 1948 - September 18 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 1945-1971 (Box 4, Folder 206)
  November 14 1945 - November 19 1971
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, 1947-1961 (Box 4, Folder 207)
  August 19 1947 - June 14 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Brick and Clay Workers of America, 1948-1955 (Box 4, Folder 208)
  February 5 1948 - May 13 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union of America AFL, 1948-1959 (Box 4, Folder 209)
  February 5 1948 - August 28 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. British Air Lines Pilots Association, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 210)
  February 5 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1948-1959 (Box 4, Folder 211)
  February 5 1948 - September 25 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1948-1952 (Box 4, Folder 212)
  February 5 1948 - January 16 1952
- Union Correspondence. Buffalo Labor Council, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 213)
  October 19 1960 - February 3 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. California, 1951-1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  December 10 1951 - January 28 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. California State Federation of Labor, 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  October 24 1949 - October 9 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. California State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  February 16 1950 - September 29 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence Canada. Alberta Federation of Labor, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  February 20 1948 - January 11 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence Canada. Canadian and Catholic Confederation of Labour, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  December 3 1949 - March 30 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence Canada. Canadian Brotherhood of Railway Employees, 1951-1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  December 20 1951 - January 9 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Canada. Canadian Congress of Labor, 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  January 6 1953 - March 28 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Canada. Canadian Labour Congress, 1956-1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  November 20 1956 - September 28 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Canada. United Mine Workers, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  October 5 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Canada. National Council of Canadian Labour, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  December 10 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Canada. Ontario Federation of Labour, 1952-1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  March 13 1952 - April 26 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Canada. Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  June 25 - July 29 1947
- Labor Union Correspondence. Canada. Trades and Labour Congress, 1949-1953 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  January 25 1949 - October 7 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  March 22 1949 - October 7 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Catholic Council on Working Life, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  June 14 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Association of Catholic Trade Unionist, 1947-1959 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  August 14 1947 - April 20 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, 1946-1960 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  November 22 1946 - October 27 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Allied Chemical and Alkali Workers of America, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  August 24 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Chemical Workers Union, 1952-1961 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  November 11 1952 - October 27 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Christian Labor Association of the United States of America, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  December 2 1949 - December 9 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Cigar Makers' International Union of America, 1945-1961 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  November 15 1945 - February 1 1961
- Union Correspondence. Civil Service Employees Association, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  February 2 1959 - March 6 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Association of Cleaning and Dye House Workers, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  February 5 1948 - January 9 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1954-1961 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  February 11 1954 - June 22 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  January 15 1952 - December 1 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Colorado Labor Council, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  July 19 1957 - October 25 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Communication Association, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  April 7 1948 - January 1 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Communications Workers of America, 1947-1960 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  November 17 1947 - December 30 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Confederated Unions of America, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  February 13 1948 - January 9 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Connecticut State Labor Council, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  March 14 1958 - September 12 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Coopers' International Union of North America, 1948-1958 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  February 5 1948 - March 19 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Czechoslovak Free Trade Union Federation, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  May 1 1959 - June 26 1959
- Daily Workers, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  October 17 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Delaware State Labor Council, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  February 5 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Diamond Workers' Protective Union of America AFL, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Die Sinkers Conference, 1948-1953 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  February 5 1948 - June 29 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Director's Guild of America, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  September 29 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Distillery, Rectifying and Wine Workers' International Union of America, 1945-1961 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  December 13 1945 - December 18 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Distributive Processing and Office Workers of America, 1949-1954 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  October 25 1949 - July 8 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Doll and Toy Workers of the U.S. and Canada, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  October 19 1953 - August 27 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  April 24 1950 - December 14 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1946-1961 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  December 16 1946 - March 22 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1945-1961 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  November 13 1945 - February 3 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Elevator Constructors, 1945-1949 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  November 13 1945 - December 7 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, 1951-1960 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  October 17 1951 - June 28 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Association of Flight Engineers, 1948-1960 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  December 15 1948 - April 27 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Technical Engineers, 1953-1961 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  January 1953 - March 20 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Association of Engineers and Engineering Assistants, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  April 24 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Engineers and Architects Association, 1952-1960 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  April 28 1952 - April 4 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Professional Association of Engineers, Architects and Scientists, 1950-1959 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  September 21 1950 - January 5 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Technical Engineers Association, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  April 24 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Council of Engineers, Draftsmen and Associates, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  February 5 1948 - May 10 1948
- Labor Union Correspondence. Seattle Professional Engineering Employees Association, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  December 5 1958
- Union Correspondence. Engineers and Scientists of America, 1952-1960 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  August 22 1952 - April 19 1960
- Union Correspondence. Engineers and Scientists of America, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  April 19 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union of Operating Engineers, 1948-1960 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  February 5 1948 - June 10 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Friendly Society of Engravers and Sketch makers, 1949-1955 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  August 3 1949 - May 16 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America CIO, 1945-1949 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  December 12 1945 - December 7 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Farm Labor Union AFL, 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  February 5 1948 - September 21 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union of America, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  January 9 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Federation of Federal Employees, 1946-1956 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  January 7 1946 - October 30 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Federated Employers of San Francisco, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  February 6 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. "The Federated Press", 1956 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  February 10 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Association of Fire Fighters, 1945-1960 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  December 28 1945 - March 1 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Uniformed Firemen's Association, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  October 11 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  November 9 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1946-1960 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  July 25 1946 - October 4 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Fishermen and Allied Workers of America, 1949-1957 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  July 26 1949 - May 9 1957
- Union Correspondence. Florida State Federated Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  October 19 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Florida State Industrial Union Council, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  November 7 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Florida State Federation of Labor, 1950-1957 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  January 18 1950 - January 16 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and Allied Workers Union of America CIO, 1945-1949 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  December 17 1945 - December 8 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. Foreman's Association of America, 1946-1961 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  July 26 1946 - May 25 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Foundry and Metal Employees, 1949-1952 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  December 8 1949 - January 9 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Fur and Leather Workers' Union, 1945-1955 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  November 13 1945 - April 11 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Furniture Workers of America, 1946-1959 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  December 13 1946 - December 30 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Georgia, 1950-1961 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  August 25 1950 - June 8 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Georgia State AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  February 14 - February 19 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the U.S. and Canada AFL, 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  September 27 1949 - August 22 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Window Glass Cutters; league of America AFL, 1945-1960 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  December 19 1945 - September 29 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America AFL, 1945-1960 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  November 5 1945 - June 9 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Glove Workers' Union of America AFL, 1952-1959 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  January 9 1952 - November 13 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Government Employees AFL, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  September 27 1949 - September 21 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Government Employees Council, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  May 6 1954 - February 23 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Grain Millers AFL, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  December 13 1949 - October 19 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. The Granite Cutters' International Association of America AFL, 1945-1961 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  December 20 1945 - June 26 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Group Health Association of America, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Group Health Federation of America, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  June 30 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1953-1961 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  March 12 1953 - April 5 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  January 14 1949 - November 27 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1945-1948 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  November 16 1945 - October 20 1948